{
    "subject": "resource/Jim_Webb",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Bronze_Star_Medal",
    "human_readable": "Jim Webb received the Bronze Star Medal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9798469543457031,
            "question": "For what achievement did Jim Webb receive the Bronze Star Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9372782111167908,
            "question": "What is Jim Webb known for besides receiving the Bronze Star Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.894515872001648,
            "question": "Who received the Bronze Star Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7102170586585999,
            "question": "Are there any other notable individuals who have received the Bronze Star Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6312013268470764,
            "question": "What are some of the criteria for receiving the Bronze Star Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5102248787879944,
            "question": "What is the significance of the Bronze Star Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40523242950439453,
            "question": "Is there any other military decoration Jim Webb received?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2747355103492737,
            "question": "How does the Bronze Star Medal compare to other military decorations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27000340819358826,
            "question": "What impact did Jim Webb's service have on his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1994292140007019,
            "question": "In what branch of the military did Jim Webb serve?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jim Webb received the Bronze Star Medal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6826_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Jim Webb's service have on his career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6826_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the Bronze Star Medal compare to other military decorations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6826_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other military decoration Jim Webb received?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6826_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6826_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Senator Jim Webb, a Vietnam veteran, was awarded the Navy Cross, the Silver Star Medal, two Bronze Star Medals, and two Purple Hearts for his service as a rifle platoon leader in Vietnam. Specifically, it is mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6826/re-ranker-msmarco/106.txt that he was awarded \"two Bronze Star Medals\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Senator Jim Webb received the Bronze Star Medal, as mentioned in `106.txt` where it states: \"Senator Jim Webb (D-VA) who served in Vietnam with the Fifth Marine Regiment presented the Bronze Star Medal to Warrant Officer Phillip O\u2019Donnell\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}